Let me tell you a story about a slime.
Slime
Lives near water
One day, the slime that Tia brought here
to purify our waste water and
sewage started to multiply,
and now there are lots of different types
of slimes that are all different colors here.
Normal
Red
Yellow
Holy
Green
Black
They were all harmless,
so I didn't really notice
that they'd been multiplying, but...
Did it drink an entire barrel?
A single slime drank it all?
Even my dad can only drink
half a barrel at most.
That alcohol was everyone's property!
You can't go and drink it
without our permission!
This deserves a severe punishment!
That's right!
Yeah!
P-please wait a minute, everyone!
Let's all calm down!
This came as a big shock to
all the alcohol-loving residents here.
And so began our village's first trial.
Guilty
Wait, um...
Let's burn it.
If we need fire, leave it to me!
Guilty.
But...
If we need fire, leave it to me!
What's going on?
Are we blowing something up?
No, let's dry it out in the sun!
Well, I feel bad for the poor thing,
so let's move away from the barbaric options...
How about we go with a
short confinement as a punishment?
Confinement
But that was our precious alcohol!
Jeez, this kind of stuff happens
because you're too soft!
Um, everyone?
We're talking about a slime here.
Even if we punish it, I'm not sure
that it's going to reflect on its actions.
Well, you have a point.
It is a slime, after all.
And so, that slime was acquitted.
I got a little too fired up back there...
After that, it began to pop up during our feasts
and celebrations so that it could join us.
Oh well. I think it's alright
if we have one slime like that.
Too many would be a problem, though.
Farming Life in Another World
When you open your eyes and see
that pure white light, the story begins
Stepping forth into a new world,
what kind of flowers will we make bloom?
Even if it's cloudy,
even if we get dirty from a puddle
We continue on
There's a future we can't imagine
waiting for us, I'm sure of it
Meeting, meeting, and connecting
If you smile,
everyone around you will smile too
Let's plant a small seed and nurture it
One day it'll become a large flower
Turn regrets and failures into fuel
So that you're overflowing with colorful happiness
We'll join hands and share
Spread across the world, Flower Ring
The season is autumn.
The summers here aren't
particularly hot or anything,
but it's still nice when things cool down a bit
and we can get some more work done.
And here's the result.
This is making me hungry.
Autumn means eating!
Hey, stop taking all the meat.
I'm eating vegetables, too!
It's delicious!
These are all new types of mushrooms
that we didn't have in Howling Village.
Man, I really love hot pots.
If we could get seafood here,
these would taste even better.
What exactly are you referring to
when you say seafood?
Let's see...
Cod
Stuff like cod or crabs or monkfish.
Crab
Monkfish
We can make broth from kombu!
Kombu
Then we could make a chanco hotpot with miso!
Start researching those things immediately!
I've found information on them!
What do I do?
I've never even seen the ocean.
Did you say crabs?
Can you eat those?
Speaking from experience
They're really hard!
Kombu...
It sounds like something terrifying.
The Raging Storm
Kombu
Broth?
That's the soup-like thing you showed me
how to prepare earlier, right?
That's right.
Is chanco a kind of fish, too?
The Deep Sea Sage
Chanco
If we need ocean access,
there's a port city within the boundaries
of the Demonic Kingdom.
You can reach it if you
head south from this village.
They do a lot of trading of ocean products,
so we might be able to find those fish there.
Okay then, I'll fly over and check it out.
I'll accompany you.
We can ask a merchant I know for help.
Let's get started right away!
I'll take care of the miso!
They all really like hotpots, huh?
Indeed.
See you later.
We're counting on you.
When it comes to food, everyone here
gets very motivated to work.
Well, nothing makes me happier as a farmer
than seeing them happily enjoying my food.
And so, the return of the group
that set out in earnest took place...
3 days later
3 days later.
Goroun Company President
Michael Goroun
My name is Michael.
I'm a merchant from the city of Shashato
in the Demonic Kingdom.
I'm the mayor, Hiraku.
Thank you for coming
all the way here to our village.
It's nothing.
This is part of my job as a merchant.
These are the marine products
I brought from the city of Shashato.
They are our pride and joy.
With regards to the seaweed
called kombu that you requested,
our fishermen normally throw it
back into the ocean
even if they pull some up in their nets.
Huh? So...
No need to worry.
I'll have my men collect some right away.
We'll have it dried and ready before long.
I see.
With regards to my visit here today,
I have three main goals.
The first is to properly greet you
and thank you for requesting
to do business with us.
The second is to suggest more opportunities
for us to trade goods and do business.
And my third goal, if possible,
is to become the official government
purveyor for this village.
Official government purveyor?
It means he wants to handle all trade
between us and the outside world.
You're being quite direct
in what you're asking us for.
I'm always careful to not be so indirect
that my intentions are misinterpreted.
All of the crops you have here
are very enticing.
If you allow me the opportunity,
I can get you several times more value
when trading them.
There are a lot of people who want
to do trade with this village.
As I said, if possible.
I'd like to ask that you first
have a look at a list of the products
that my company handles the trading of.
And from there,
we can discuss my proposition.
We were able to cover a lot of
important ground with today's talks.
Next time, I'd like it if we were able to
discuss the alcohol produced in this village...
You can't have the alcohol!
Pardon me.
I'll leave things here for today.
Well, he seemed like
a skilled merchant, didn't he?
Yeah.
It'll be a big help having him
handle our negotiations.
And even though he's handling things for us,
we'll end up getting more goods
when we trade now!
It really didn't seem like he had
any intention of trying to deceive us.
Yeah. I hope our relationship with him
goes smoothly from here on out.
It seemed like he was
really frightened there at the end...
but oh well.
That's to be expected
when you're talking to a dragon.
The Great Tree Village, huh?
That was scary!
3 days earlier
Shashato City
A visitor?
Without an appointment?
Yes.
They'd like to talk business with you.
I couldn't be any busier now.
My name is Michael Goroun.
I work as the head of the largest
trading company in this city.
If it's nothing major,
can't you guys handle it?
Why do they need to see me specifically?
They requested you by name
when they arrived.
They've even brought goods from their farm.
I wasn't sure what to do.
They already brought goods with them?
Don't they know the rules?
If you guys can't handle it on your own,
then just refer them somewhere el-
No, I'll meet with them.
Huh? Okay.
My merchant's intuition is telling me
that I can't ignore this.
This strange feeling
welling up inside of me is...
I'm so glad that you remember me.
Of course.
If I remember correctly,
the last time we had the pleasure of meeting
was at your birthday party.
I can't believe the young lady of
the Chrome family is here.
My head would have rolled
if I'd have sent her away.
And who have you brought with you?
Oh, she's...
I'm Lastismoon of the dragons.
Please call me Lasty.
Lastismoon?!
Could she really be that crazy dragon?
Crazy Dragon Lastismoon
She's just a child!
The daughter of one of the most powerful
families of the Demonic Kingdom
and a dangerous dragon.
The risks of trading with them are too high.
Risk
So what brings you here today?
But I can't just ignore them!
We'd like you to purchase these from us.
And in exchange for them,
there are some things we'd like you to find.
What's going on here?
I'm being stared down by a dragon
while being surrounded by lizardmen.
I'm about to enter
some outrageous trade talks.
Was that feeling I had before
a warning of impending danger?
These are...
those fruit that have entered
the Demonic Kingdom
that people have been talking about!
Each one of these
can fetch several silver coins.
And look how many they've brought!
Risk
The goods you wanted
were from the ocean, correct?
That's right!
This port is my territory.
I can find you whatever you need.
Because that's...
the job of a merchant!
I can't let this chance get away!
Hey you. Go to the port and bring me
their best catches from this morning.
Okay!
And after that begin preparing
for me to travel.
Uh, okay!
I'll take part in the delivery myself.
Are the goods going to the capital?
No, they're going to The Great Tree Village
in The Forest of Death.
I'll carry the stuff,
so I can give you a ride too.
Forest of Death?
Unease
Risk
Give me a ride?
He's a merchant from Shashato.
Oh, the merchant came with you?
Illegal Demon Spider
Killer Angels
Angel of Annihilation
Inferno Wolf
The mayor seems normal.
Vampire Princess
You can't have the alcohol!
I-I survived it...
I managed to finish my business
with that terrifying group
while having a smile on my face.
That was the best deal of my life.
Huge profits are waiting for me
from here on out.
However...
I'm not sure if my body can handle this.
Here it is, real seafood!
Maybe next time I'll ask him
for shrimp or squid.
This is the third time a dragon
has attacked this village.
I think.
Is this one related to Dryme again?
For the record, the three angel squad
in charge of patrolling the skies
was quickly able to spot this dragon.
However stopping a dragon
proved to be difficult.
But seriously, what is that dragon doing?
Acting smug?
Okay, so you're challenging me.
You want a fight, right?
In that case...
I missed?!
...is what I want them to think.
Once more!
Defeated.
Ouch...
Aw, you got me.
I surrender!
Just kidding!
Why did you do that?
Well you see,
it really isn't that big of an issue.
But you burned the forest?
Okay then, just give me a minute
and I'll come up with
a super important reason why I did that.
Hey!
Wait a minute, mayor!
I'm sorry, she's...
It's little Drymey!
Little?
Explaining
According to Dryme's explanation,
her name is Hakuren.
She's his older sister.
This is your fault, you know.
You said you were giving away
Lasty as a bride.
Bride?
No, I...
You totally said it!
You said you wanted to marry her off
to the mayor of this village someday!
Dryme?
It's not like that!
I might have said something kind of like that
while I was drinking, but...
I'll do it one day for the prosperity of our tribe!
I might have said something kind of like that
while I was drinking, but...
I'll do it one day for the prosperity of our tribe!
As the person in question,
it makes it really hard to comment on this.
So that's why I came out here
to see what kind of person
he was marrying her off to.
Then why couldn't you just
come visit normally?
Everyone always talks about
how strong the mayor here is,
so I wanted to come play with you a little.
It's not just that.
She's mostly here to vent anger.
Of course I am!
Do you think I could just let it slide
that my little niece is going to find
a husband before I do?!
I mean come on,
she's 900 years younger than me!
900 Years Older
900 Years Younger
I can't accept this!
It's ridiculous!
Don't you agre-
It's fine if you want to come play,
but you shouldn't be causing
problems for people.
And it goes without saying, that you're
going to clean up this mess, right?
Okay, I get it!
And it goes without saying, that you're
going to clean up this mess, right?
Clean Up
So you two are always eating food
that tastes this good?
Well, I'm not always
imposing on everyone here.
Only about three out of every ten days.
Wow, lucky!
Maybe it's five days...
She's already fitting in...
Five days?!
Mayor.
I'm sorry that my aunt is-
Hey, Lasty?
...that Big Sis Hakuren
is causing so much trouble.
It's nothing you need to
apologize about, Lasty.
Oh right, I heard you have some
really fun games here.
Like the one where you line up
the little square things.
You mean mahjong?
I want to try that.
You play with four people, right?
Hey mayor, let's play!
I don't want to leave here
only having lost to you!
Fine by me.
So, first let me explain the rules.
I'll be fine!
I can figure it out!
Really?
But more importantly...
what should we bet?
I see.
This way it's more fun
than just playing the game.
I think we should take it easy at first...
Mayor.
What would you normally bet
when playing mahjong like this?
Even if you want me to bet something,
I don't really have anything I can bet.
So then should we have
a punishment for the loser?
The only thing I can think to do
is play strip mahjong.
That sounds great!
So the loser gets a taste of humiliation.
No, no, I don't want to force anyone
to do anything they don't want to!
Right, Lasty?
If we're competing,
then there's no way I can lose...
Excuse me, Lasty?
...as a member of the dragon clan!
I have a feeling that
things are going to get bad.
Ah, that's chii!
That's riichi!
Too bad... ron!
What?!
This is my fault for carelessly
suggesting this idea.
This is indeed shameful.
The dragons are all very competitive,
Aw, I was so close.
and they can't stand losing.
Let's keep going!
This led to a very serious game
of strip mahjong starting.
You're new to this, aren't you?
And you're wearing the least clothing.
How are you so confident?!
Now that it's come to this,
I wanted to carefully rack up some points
and end things while maintaining
the peace, but...
something isn't right.
Seriously, what's happening here?
How am I losing?!
I'm on my last piece of clothing!
Don't tell me they're using
some kind of magic trickery?!
Are they using telekinesis to rewrite the tiles?!
Can they see through the back of my tiles?!
No.
There isn't anything written on this one.
Is it an extra?
I'm overthinking it.
Some tiles are just like that.
In any case,
my chance has finally arrived.
I can score a double yakuman.
I can end the whole thing
with a single move.
But...
Sad Memories
of course it had to be this tile again!
It doesn't matter.
I'll never beat the dragons
if I'm paralyzed by fear!
Ron!
That's about right.
Okay, pants off!
Pants off! Pants off! Pants off!
I am defeated!
The dragons are gathering
in that village again?
Yes. The ancient dragon Hakuren
was spotted as well.
No way... They're got enough power
to conquer a whole country now.
Can we afford to simply sit back and watch?
More importantly, Beezel...
Yes. Do you have an idea?
No.
Demon Lord Galgardo
It's my daughter.
She's been in a bad mood lately.
She hasn't said anything to me all day
besides good morning.
Is this her rebellious phase?
So anyways... we need to focus on
preparing our military forces immediately!
We'll need to secure the funds we need-
I resign. Signed Randan.
Letter of Resignation
Randan?!
I resign. Signed Randan.
Ah, he ran away.
Is this a joke?!
So if you divide these apples
between three people,
how many apples will you have to eat?
I really wish I could just them all, though!
She's really come into her own here.
After attacking The Great Tree Village,
Hakuren decided to stay here
for the time being.
My Room
Signed by Hakuren
Surprisingly, she's very skilled
and able to handle any job here.
There we go. Nice and easy.
Surprisingly, she's very skilled
and able to handle any job here.
There we go. Nice and easy.
The Great Tree Village by Hakuren
But she complains about
anything she's asked to do.
Every time I turn around,
she's in her room doing nothing.
I don't wanna to it.
Why do you complain so much?
I'm hoping that one day maybe people
will stop asking me to do things.
I had no choice but to order her to start
digging holes and then filling them back in.
Okay, enough! I give up!
I had no choice but to order her to start
digging holes and then filling them back in.
Okay, enough! I give up!
She gave up on day one.
In the end we settled on her teaching
reading, writing, and math.
She became the village teacher.
And that's why learning to
read, write, and do math,
will help you all a lot
in your day to day lives!
Listen up, I want all of you
to work really hard,
so that one day I don't have to
work anymore, okay?
Okay!
I think her motivation
might not be the greatest.
Please, we beg of you to spare our lives.
What are you talking about?
According to the lamia girls...
at some point, the younger animals
decided to clear a dungeon they found
in the middle of the forest..
And then the lamia were forced to
quickly flee their homes.
Praise me
They didn't know what they were doing,
but they still caused the girls
a lot of trouble.
What should we do?
They came all the way here
to seek our aid and protection.
I don't think it would be proper
to turn them away.
In the end, we decided to trade
the precious gems the lamia mined
for some of our crops.
After that, they went back to
their original homes.
I'd appreciate it if we could
keep trading from now on.
Of course!
Just ask us for whatever you want!
They're so genuinely excited about this
that it's making me awkward.
Okay then, I have something
I'd like to request.
Yes?
It's fine if it's only when
you're visiting here,
but I'd appreciate it if you could
put some clothes on.
That might be part of their culture,
but I really had trouble not staring.
After that, the lamia formed
the Lamia Delivery Service
and started carrying
our trading goods for us.
With everything said and done,
I'm glad we found some reliable neighbors.
Between this and the increased trade
with other cities and areas,
it really feels like the village
has reached a new level.
Since we've increased
the amount of trade we're doing,
how about we plant more crops?
Yeah.
It appears that village is indeed
amassing military might
and planning something foul!
They may be convincing
Flowrem to stay there
so that they can use her as
a hostage if they need to!
We should begin gathering
our troops at once, Princess!
I understand.
We must defeat that village
and save Flowrem.
I can feel the soft seasonal winds,
gently on my fingertips
Let's search for what we love
in the clouds floating in the sky
Forget about the hands of the clock for now
Try taking one deep breath
The rainbow-colored scenery
will resonate with my heart
I'm sure any wish I have will come true
Because you're by my side
You make every day feel like a dream
At that warm and kind place
Keep showing me your smiling face forever
Next Time
Episode 10
Princess Yuri
Next Time